[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the traditional Spanish dish Cocido Madrileno?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken", "Pork", "Beef"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The International Space Station is a joint project of five space agencies, including NASA. Which Space Agency is not part of the project?", "correct_answer": "China National Space Administration", "incorrect_answers": ["Russian Federal Space Agency", "Canadian Space Agency", "Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The manatee has a tail similar in shape to that of the dolphin.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What motto do North Carolina license plates carry?", "correct_answer": "First In Flight", "incorrect_answers": ["The Old North State", "Nothing Finer", "Tarheel State"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bacillus Thuringiensis, which is usually found naturally in the soil, is used as this.", "correct_answer": "Insecticide", "incorrect_answers": ["Beer additive", "Food additive", "Wine ferment agent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prometea, an example of successfully cloned mammal, was what type of animal?", "correct_answer": "Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Cat", "Pig", "Rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cheetahs are only found in Africa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 2003 MTV music awards these two stars wore diamond necklaces with their initials.", "correct_answer": "Britney Spears and Madonna", "incorrect_answers": ["Alicia Keys and Anastasia", "Whitney Huston and Mariah Carey", "Jeniffer Aniston and Brad Pitt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which art term is also used to refer to dependencies between computer applications or processes?", "correct_answer": "Choreography", "incorrect_answers": ["Screenplay", "Directing", "Libretto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Chinese city, the capital of Hubei province, lies at the confluence of the Yangtze River and Han River.", "correct_answer": "Wuhan", "incorrect_answers": ["Xia Jong", "Fujian", "Shanghai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actress voiced the Queen Ant in the 2006 animated movie The Ant Bully?", "correct_answer": "Meryl Streep", "incorrect_answers": ["Jane Fonda", "Susan Sarandon", "Kate Winslet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The lightest baby weighed this much.", "correct_answer": "9.87 ounce (280 g)", "incorrect_answers": ["17.63 ounce (500 g)", "0.70 ounce (20 g)", "3.88 ounce (110 g)"]}]